A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39; 234.9 Cubic Feet 597 containers
  - Rockefeller Family, 1987-1991; 26; 36.34 Cubic Feet 56 letter document boxes and 32 legal document boxes
    - Laurance S. Rockefeller (and family), 7
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits and Appreciation, 1989 (Box 512, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1988 (Box 512, Folder 3)
      - Property - JY Ranch - Visits, 1987 (Box 512, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - Massachusetts - Martha's Vineyard - Chasin Sale to LSR (Box 512, Folder 6)
      - Property - Massachusetts - Martha's Vineyard - Martha's Vineyard Development (Box 513, Folder 1)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - A-Z (Box 513, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Board of Directors (Box 513, Folder 4)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Account 2 (Box 514, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Basement (Water Problem) (Box 514, Folder 3)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Delorean, John Z. (Box 515, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Finances (Box 515, Folder 3, Box 516, Folder 1-2)
      - Property - New York City - 834 Fifth Avenue - Meetings (Box 516, Folder 3)
      - Property - New York City - 620 Park Avenue, 1980-1988 (Box 516, Folder 4)
      - Property - New York State - Beaverkill (Box 518, Folder 1)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 517, Folder 1)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Outer Lodge (Parcel C-19, C-19A, C-21) (Box 517, Folder 2)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Sale by LSR to DR of Parcels C-3 and C-23 (Box 517, Folder 3)
      - Property - Pocantico Hills - Lucy R. Waletzky's Pond-Stillman Park (Box 531, Folder 1)
        Restricted Living Rockefeller family Family matters - Restricted for Life
      - Property - Rockwood Hall (Box 518, Folder 2)
      - Property - Tarrytown (Box 518, Folder 3)
      - Property - St. John (Box 518, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - A-D (Box 518, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - E-Z (Box 519, Folder 1-5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Agenda (Box 520, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Articles-Clippings-Printed Matter (Box 520, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Dairy (Box 520, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm (Box 520, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm - Finances (Box 520, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Debevoise, Thomas M. 2nd (Box 520, Folder 6)
      - Property - Woodstock - Finances (Box 520, Folder 7, Box 521, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - French Property (Box 531, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - The Mansion (Box 521, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Memos (Box 521, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Winks, Robin W. (Box 521, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum (Box 521, Folder 5, Box 522, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - A-L (Box 521, Folder 6-7)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - M-Z (Box 522, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Cambridge Associates (Box 522, Folder 3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Finances (Box 522, Folder 4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Long Range Plan (Box 522, Folder 5)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Monthly Report (Box 523, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Printed Matter (Box 523, Folder 2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - A-Z (Box 523, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees (Box 523, Folder 4)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation (Box 523, Folder 5, Box 524, Folder 1)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Contributions (Box 524, Folder 2)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Finances (Box 524, Folder 3)
      - Woodstock Foundation - Meetings (Box 525, Folder 1-4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn (Box 526, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - A-Z (Box 526, Folder 2-3)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Expansion (Box 526, Folder 4, Box 527, Folder 1)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Inn - Expansion - Phase I (Box 527, Folder 2)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Resort Corporation - A-Z (Box 527, Folder 3-4)
      - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Finances, 1986-1991 (Box 528, Folder 1-2, Box 529, Folder 1-4, Box 530, Folder 1)
      - Property - Wyoming (Box 530, Folder 2)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - A-Z (Box 530, Folder 3)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Landscaping (Box 530, Folder 4)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Photos (Box 530, Folder 5)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1991 (Box 531, Folder 3)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits and Appreciation, 1990 (Box 531, Folder 4-5)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1989 (Box 531, Folder 6)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1988 (Box 531, Folder 7)
      - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1987 (Box 531, Folder 8)
      - Schedules (Box 530, Folder 6)
      - Purchases (Box 530, Folder 7)
      - Trips - A-E (Box 530, Folder 8)
      - Trips - F-Z (Box 532, Folder 1-2)
      - Trips - Caribbean (Box 532, Folder 3-4)
      - Trips - Europe (Box 532, Folder 5, Box 533, Folder 1)
      - Trips - Mexico (Box 533, Folder 2)
      - Trips - USSR, 1989 (Box 533, Folder 3, Box 534, Folder 1-3, Box 535, Folder 1)
      - Trusts, 1980-1991 (Box 536, Folder 1-4)
        Restricted - Estate Matters - Weber Family
      - Works of Art - A-Z (Box 535, Folder 2-3)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Addresses-Remarks-Statements (Box 535, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Awards (Box 535, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - A-Z (Box 537, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Dinners-Luncheons (Box 537, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Mary French - Investments (Box 537, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - A-Z (Box 491, Folder 4)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - Beaverkill Project (Box 491, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller, Laurance (Larry) - Charitable Lead Trust A-Z (Box 491, Folder 6)
      - Chasin, Richard and Laura (Box 458, Folder 5)
      - Laura R. Chasin Charitable Lead Trust (Box 460, Folder 1)
      - Ortiz, Carlos Alejandro and Mrs. Rachel French (Box 463, Folder 6)
      - Waletzky, Lucy R. (Box 548, Folder 4)
      - Weber, Warren and Mrs. Marion R. (Box 548, Folder 5)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller (and family), 8
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - A-Z (Box 537, Folder 4)
      - Biography (Box 537, Folder 5)
      - Trust for Children 1976 - Texas Trust, 1976 October 20 (Box 538, Folder 3)
      - Works of Art - Mexican Collection (Box 538, Folder 4)
      - Estate (Box 539, Folder 1)
      - Estate - Attica Litigation (Box 539, Folder 2)
      - Estate - Monte Sacro (Box 539, Folder 3)
      - Rockefeller, Happy - A-Z (Box 537, Folder 6)
      - Morgan, Mary R. (Box 463, Folder 3)
      - Pierson, Joseph A. (Box 463, Folder 7)
      - Roberts, Ann R. (Box 463, Folder 8)
      - Rockefeller, Ingrid R. (Box 486, Folder 6)
        Restricted Living Rockefeller family Personal Restricted for Life
      - Rockefeller, Jennifer (Box 486, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Michael S. (Box 538, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Mark (Box 538, Folder 2)
      - Rockefeller, Rodman C. (Box 537, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, Peter C. (Box 538, Folder 5)
        Restricted Peter C. Rockefeller
      - Rockefeller, Steven C. (Box 538, Folder 8)
      - Rockefeller, Steven C. - Charitable Lead Trusts - A-Z (Box 538, Folder 9)
      - Rockefeller, Steven C., Jr. (Box 538, Folder 10)
        Restricted - Personal - Restricted for Life
    - Winthrop Rockefeller (and family), 9
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 537, Folder 8)
      - Estate - Winrock International (Box 540, Folder 1-2)
      - Estate - Winrock International - Cousins (Box 548, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul (Box 540, Folder 3)
      - Estate - Winthrop Rockefeller Charitable Trust (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1987-1991; 27; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 541, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A-E (Box 541, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - F-Z (Box 542, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Reports, 1987, 1990, 1991 (Box 542, Folder 3)
    - Board of Trustees - A-Z (Box 543, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees - A-Z - Cousins (Box 548, Folder 6)
    - By-Laws (Box 543, Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Colin (Box 543, Folder 3)
    - Contributions (Box 543, Folder 4)
    - Contributions - Cousins (Box 548, Folder 7)
    - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation (Box 543, Folder 5)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1991 (Box 543, Folder 6)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 544, Folder 1-3)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 545, Folder 1-3)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1987 (Box 546, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Fund, 1987-1991; 28; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - David Rockefeller Fund (Box 546, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1987-1991; 29; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller Family Fund - A-Z (Box 546, Folder 3)
    - Contributions - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 548, Folder 8)
    - Meetings-Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 546, Folder 4, Box 547, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller family office (Room 5600), 1987-1991; 30; 5.32 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller Family Office - A-Z (Box 547, Folder 2-4)
    - 5600, Inc. (Box 548, Folder 9)
    - 5600, Inc. - Meetings-Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 549, Folder 1-3)
    - Personnel A-Z (Box 539, Folder 4)
      Restricted - Personnel material - Open in 2061
    - Philanthropic Office (Box 548, Folder 10)
    - David Rockefeller - Office Refurbishing, 1986-1988 (Box 539, Folder 5)
      Restricted - Personnel material - Open in 2056
    - Rockefeller and Company - A-L (Box 550, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - M-Z (Box 551, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Associates Capital Fund (Box 550, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Discovery Fund (Box 551, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - 5500 Fund (Box 551, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Finances (Box 552, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Investment Newsletter (Box 552, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 552, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Meetings-Minutes (Box 552, Folder 4, Box 553, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Odyssey Fund (Box 553, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pioneer Investment Trust (Box 553, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pioneer II Fund (Box 553, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pioneer III Fund (Box 553, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Pocantico and Discovery Fund (Box 553, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Rockefeller Balanced Fund (Box 553, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller and Company - Rockefeller Capital Fund (Box 554, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates (Box 554, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Financial Services (Box 554, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company (Box 554, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company - Finances (Box 554, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company - Meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 554, Folder 6, Box 555, Folder 1-2)
    - Venrock - A-Z (Box 556, Folder 1)
    - Venrock - Finances (Box 556, Folder 2)
    - Public Affairs - A-Z (Box 556, Folder 3-4)
    - Public Affairs - Forbes Magazine (Box 557, Folder 1-3)
    - Public Affairs - Greensward Foundation, Inc. (Box 557, Folder 4)
    - Public Affairs - Summary of Media Coverage (Box 558, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - A-M (Box 558, Folder 2-4)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - N-Z (Box 559, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs - Requests - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Credo (Box 558, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1987-1991; 31; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Rockefeller Foundation - A-Z (Box 559, Folder 2-3)
  - Rockefeller University, 1987-1991; 32; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Rockefeller University - A-Z (Box 560, Folder 1-2)
    - Baltimore, David (Box 560, Folder 3)
    - Contributions (Box 560, Folder 4)
    - Contributions - Cousins (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - Council (Box 561, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising (Box 561, Folder 2)
    - King of Thailand Biomedical Fellowship (Box 561, Folder 3)
    - Printed Matter (Box 561, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 561, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Contributions (Box 561, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Contributions - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 566, Folder 2-3)
  - S, 1987-1991; 33; 3.8 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes
    - S - Miscellaneous (Box 561, Folder 7)
    - Science - A-B (Box 561, Folder 8-9)
    - Science - C-Z (Box 562, Folder 1-2)
    - Science - A-Z - Cousins (Box 566, Folder 4-6)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest (Box 562, Folder 3)
    - Science - Center for Science in the Public Interest - Cousins (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Science - Committee for Responsible Genetics (Box 566, Folder 8)
    - Science - Institute of Noetic Sciences (Box 563, Folder 1-3, Box 564, Box 565, Folder 1)
    - Science - International Student Pugwash, Inc. (Box 566, Folder 9)
    - Science - National Academy of Sciences (Box 565, Folder 2)
    - Science - New Alchemy Institute (Box 567, Folder 1)
    - Science - New York Hall of Science (Box 565, Folder 3)
    - Science - Union of Concerned Scientists (Box 567, Folder 2)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-Z (Box 565, Folder 4)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - A-Z - Cousins (Box 567, Folder 3)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - Island Foundation (Box 565, Folder 5)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - Seal Harbor Fire Department (Box 565, Folder 6)
    - Seal Harbor Organizations - Seal Harbor Fire Department - Cousins (Box 567, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations (Box 568, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Board of Trustees (Box 568, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Contributions (Box 568, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Finances (Box 568, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 568, Folder 5)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Fund Raising - Event at the Plaza, 1987 November 2 (Box 568, Folder 6)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings (Box 569, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Annual, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 2)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Executive Committee, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 3)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Program Committee, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Property Committee, 1987 (Box 569, Folder 5-6)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Meetings - Property Committee, 1987 (Box 570, Folder 1)
    - Sleepy Hollow Restorations - Montgomery Place (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - T-W, 1987-1991; 34; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - T - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 3)
    - U - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 4)
    - V - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 5)
    - W - Miscellaneous (Box 570, Folder 6)
    - Westchester Organizations - A-Z (Box 582, Folder 5)
  - Welfare, 1987-1991; 35; 5.32 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes
    - Welfare - A-C (Box 570, Folder 7-8)
    - Welfare - C-Z (Box 571, Folder 1-4)
    - Welfare - A-Z - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 1-6)
      Restricted - David Rockefeller, Jr.
    - American Red Cross (Box 571, Folder 5)
    - Center for Community Change (Box 579, Folder 7)
    - Community Service Society of New York (Box 572, Folder 1)
    - The Hope Program (Box 572, Folder 2)
    - Institut Henry-Dunant, Geneva (Box 572, Folder 3)
    - New York City - Department for the Aging (Citymeals-on-Wheels) (Box 572, Folder 4)
    - New York City - Department for the Aging - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 579, Folder 8-9)
    - United Service Organizations, Inc. (USO) (Box 572, Folder 5)
    - United Service Organizations (USO) of Metropolitan New York (Box 573, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Nurse Service of New York (Box 573, Folder 2)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. (Box 573, Folder 3)
    - Animals - A-Z (Box 573, Folder 4)
    - Animals - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 579, Folder 10-11)
    - Animals - Animal Medical Center (Box 573, Folder 5)
    - Animals - Scientists Center for Animal Welfare (Box 574, Folder 1)
    - Animals - Scientists Center for Animal Welfare - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 12)
    - Blind - A-Z (Box 574, Folder 2)
    - Community Centers - A-L (Box 574, Folder 3-4)
    - Community Centers - M-Z (Box 575, Folder 1)
    - Community Centers - A-L - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 13-14)
    - Community Centers - Union Settlement Association (Box 575, Folder 2)
    - Crime Prevention - A-Z (Box 575, Folder 3-5)
    - Crime Prevention - A-E - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 15-16)
    - Crime Prevention - National Victim Center (Box 575, Folder 6, Box 576, Folder 1)
    - Day Nurseries (Box 576, Folder 2)
    - Day Nurseries - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 17)
    - Day Nurseries - Children's Storefront (Box 576, Folder 3)
    - Day Nurseries - Children's Storefront - Cousins (Box 579, Folder 18)
    - Family Counseling (Box 576, Folder 4)
    - Family Counseling - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 579, Folder 19-20)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service of Westchester (Box 576, Folder 5)
    - Family Counseling - Family Service of Westchester - Cousins (Box 567, Folder 5)
    - Handicapped - A-Z (Box 577, Folder 1-4)
    - Handicapped - A-Z - Cousins (Box 567, Folder 6-9)
    - Handicapped - International Center for Disabled (ICD) (Box 577, Folder 5)
    - Handicapped - New York League for the Hard of Hearing (Box 578, Folder 1)
    - Homes - A-Z (Box 578, Folder 2-3)
    - Homes - A-O - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 567, Folder 10-11)
    - Homes - P-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 580, Folder 1-2)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - A-Z (Box 578, Folder 4)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - A-Z - Cousins (Box 580, Folder 3)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - Indian Law Resource Center (Box 578, Folder 5)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - Indian Law Resource Center - Cousins (Box 580, Folder 4)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - Institute for Resource Management (Box 580, Folder 5)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - Redsun Institute (Box 581, Folder 1-2)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - Seventh Generation Fund for Indian Development, Inc. (Box 581, Folder 3)
    - (American) Indians/Native Americans - Seventh Generation Fund for Indian Development, Inc. - Cousins (Box 580, Folder 6)
    - Legal - A-Z (Box 581, Folder 4)
    - Legal - A-Z - Cousins (Box 580, Folder 7)
    - Legal - Pacific Legal Foundation (Box 581, Folder 5)
    - Musicians - A-Z (Box 582, Folder 1)
    - Orphans - A-Z (Box 582, Folder 2)
    - Orphans - A-Z - Cousins (Box 580, Folder 8)
    - United Funds - A-Z (Box 582, Folder 3-4)
    - United Funds - A-Z - Cousins (Box 580, Folder 9)
    - United Way of Tri-State (Box 582, Folder 4)
    - United Funds - United Way of the Tri-State - Cousins (Box 580, Folder 10)
  - Women, 1987-1991; 36; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
    - Women - A-Z (Box 583, Folder 1)
    - Women - A-Z - Cousins (Box 586, Folder 1)
    - Catalyst (Box 582, Folder 6)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women (Box 583, Folder 2)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women, Inc. - Cousins (Box 586, Folder 2)
    - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 583, Folder 3)
    - National Women's Health Network (Box 583, Folder 4)
    - National Women's Health Network - Cousins (Box 586, Folder 3)
  - Youth, 1987-1991; 37; 3.42 Cubic Feet 8 letter document boxes and 2 half-letter document boxes
    - Youth - A-Z, 1
      - Youth - A-D (Box 584, Folder 1-4)
      - Youth - E-Z (Box 585, Folder 1-3)
      - Youth - A-Z - Cousins (Box 586, Folder 4-9)
      - Boys Club of New York (Box 585, Folder 4)
      - Boys Club of St. Croix (Box 587, Folder 1)
      - Boys Clubs of America (Box 587, Folder 2)
      - Boy Scouts of America (Box 587, Folder 3)
      - Boy Scouts of America - Cousins (Box 586, Folder 10)
      - Children's Aid Society (Box 587, Folder 4)
      - Children's Aid Society - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 586, Folder 11-12)
      - Covenant House (Box 588, Folder 1-2)
      - Covenant House - Fifth Generation (Box 586, Folder 13)
      - Girl Scouts of America (Box 588, Folder 3)
      - Graham-Windham Services to Families and Children (Box 588, Folder 4)
      - Infant Formula Action Coalition (INFACT) (Box 586, Folder 14)
      - Junior Achievement (Box 589, Folder 1)
      - Junior Achievement, Inc. - Cousins (Box 586, Folder 15)
      - Hugh O'Brian Youth Foundation (Box 589, Folder 2)
      - Police Athletic League, Inc. (Box 589, Folder 3)
      - Chi Chi Rodriguez Youth Foundation (Box 589, Folder 4)
      - Save the Children Foundation (Box 589, Folder 5)
      - Save the Children Federation - Cousins (Box 586, Folder 16)
      - Vocational Foundation (Box 590, Folder 1)
      - YMCA - A-Z (Box 590, Folder 2)
      - YMCA - A-Z - Cousins (Box 593, Folder 1)
      - YMCA - Greater New York (Box 590, Folder 3)
      - YMCA - Greater New York - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 593, Folder 2-3)
      - YWCA (Box 590, Folder 4)
      - YWCA - Hawaii Island YWCA (Box 590, Folder 5)
      - YWCA - National Board (Box 591, Folder 1)
      - YWCA - National Board - Contributions (Box 591, Folder 2)
      - YMCA - National Board - Contributions - Cousins (Box 593, Folder 4)
      - YWCA - New York City (Box 591, Folder 3)
      - YWCA - New York City - Cousins (Box 593, Folder 5)
      - YWCA - New York City - Printed Matter (Box 591, Folder 4)
      - The Youth Project (Box 593, Folder 6)
    - Camps, 2
      - Camps (Box 591, Folder 5)
      - Camps - Cousins (Box 593, Folder 7)
      - The Fresh Air Fund (Box 592, Folder 1)
      - The Fresh Air Fund - Cousins (Box 593, Folder 8)
    - Homes, 3
      - Homes (Box 592, Folder 2)
      - Homes - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 593, Folder 9-10)
  - Y-Z, 1987-1991; 38; 0.57 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box and 1 half-letter document box
    - Y - Miscellaneous (Box 583, Folder 5)
    - Z - Miscellaneous (Box 592, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera, 1940-1988; 39; 2.1 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box and 2 oversize boxes
    - Basic Needs Corporate Records and Seal (Box 594, Folder 1)
    - State of New York - Legislative Resolution 483, Mourning the death of John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1978 July 17 (Box 594, Folder 2)
    - California Historical Society - Education, Health and Welfare Award to John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1988 June 19 (Box 594, Folder 3)
    - Fordham University - A Century of Culture (Box 594, Folder 4)
    - The Arts and American Business: A Statement to Corporations, by John D. Rockefeller 3rd (Box 594, Folder 5)
    - Spelman College - Spelman Mesenger, 1951 (Box 594, Folder 6)
    - Vesmar, 1949 (Box 594, Folder 7)
    - Virgin Island - Heritage Series Number One - The Virgins: A Descriptive and Historical Profile (Box 594, Folder 8)
    - Order of the Rising Sun 5th Class, Presented by the Emperor of Japan (Box 594, Folder 9)
      Scope and Contents
      David Rockefeller noted that this was presented to either his father John D. Rockefeller Jr, or his mother, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.